{
    "name": "Read Real Japanese: Essays", 
    "vocab": [
        {
            "answer": "(ひつよう) necessary", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "必要", 
            "tried": 1
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(舌打ち) したうち", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "to cluck one's tongue", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(けっか) result", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "結果", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(解決策) かいけつさく", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "solution", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(焦がす) to burn", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "こがす", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(したうち) to cluck one's tongue", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "舌打ち", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to adjust", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "つくろう", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あらげる", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "to raise one's voice", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "to raise one's voice", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "あらげる", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(必要) ひつよう", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "necessary", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(納得が行く) to be satisfied", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "なっとくがいく", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(なべ) sauce pan", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "鍋", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "tremendous", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "すきまじい", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(比例) ひれい", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "proportion", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(解決策) solution", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "かいけつさく", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(鍋) sauce pan", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "なべ", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(結果) result", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "けっか", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(必要) necessary", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "ひつよう", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(焦がす) こがす", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "to burn", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(ひれい) proportion", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "比例", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(鍋) なべ", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "sauce pan", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つくろう", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "to adjust", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(なっとくがいく) to be satisfied", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "納得が行く", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(結果) けっか", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "result", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(かいけつさく) solution", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "解決策", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(納得が行く) なっとくがいく", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "to be satisfied", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(舌打ち) to cluck one's tongue", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "したうち", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(比例) proportion", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "ひれい", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すきまじい", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "tremendous", 
            "tried": 0
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "(こがす) to burn", 
            "failed": 0, 
            "question": "焦がす", 
            "tried": 0
        }
    ]
}